

# Sunil Chaudhari

QA TEST LEAD / COORDINATOR / MANAGER

#### **PROFILE**

Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC).

Lead/Sr QA Tester with 13+ years of experience in various Client/Server, Web, eCommerce, Web Portals & Product Companies. Possesses strong Functional, Technical, and Test management experience.

Developed Test Plans, Test Strategy, Test Scenarios, Test Cases, Test Requirements, and documentation from business, technical and functional requirements. Proficient in Manual Testing and Automated Testing. Also, act as Scrum Master.

#### **CONTACT**

sunilibn@gmail.com



in sunilchaudhari21

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### RunOps Manager

ZIMETRICS May 2020-Till Date

1.Managing DevOps and RunOps Team. Defining SLA of each type of ticket/request. Also, track for AMI Upgrades of AWS EC2 Machines.

2.Communicate with stakeholders, clients, leaders, and owners of the tickets. Define, maintain and document knowledge artifacts.

#### QA Lead

#### MARKET LOGIC SOFTWARE

Aug 2018-May 2020

1.Handling the Entire QA team from Pune Office. Responsible for UAT automation.
2.API Automation, Prioritizing Deployment in Production. CI/CD Pipeline daily activity..
3.Managing weekly release regression Cycle. Design and execution of the Test Plan. Engage proactively with QA Manager regarding project statuses, resourcing, risks.
4.Report to QA Director on a weekly basis by way of structured reports and informal meetings outlining.

#### Sr. QA Engineer

#### APPDIRECT INDIA PVT LTD

Oct 2016-Aug 2018

1.Handling Entire Module of the Product. Responsible for all QA projects and deliverables. Prioritizing Deployment in Production.

2.Managing Weekly Release regression Cycle. Design and execution of the Test Plan.
3.Helping the Product Team with the new feature development.

# Sr.Software QA Engineer

# PUBMATIC INDIA PVT LTD

Feb 2010-Jan 2016

1.Wrote SQL queries to test the application for data integrity and verified the contents of the data table. Setting 2.up UAT and responsible for UAT process.

3.Design test cases and execute the tests. Defines scope and objectives of all levels of QA testing. 4.Write, automate and maintain and execute performance test cases using JMeter, Bugzilla, and other technologies/tools.

## System Engineer

## S1 SERVICES INDIA

Aug 2008-Jan-2010

1.Product Support and JIRA Admin.

2.Administration Support for Testing Tools like JIRA, Quality Centre.

3.Maintaining customer relationships & satisfaction.

## **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor Of Computer Science

FERGUSSON COLLEGE, PUNE

2001-2005

## SKILLS



Team Management - Team Building



Manual-Functional-UI-DB-API Testing, SC



Operations-Support



AWS cost management , ELK Stack



Agile, SCRUM, JIRA



Scrum Master - Project Coordinator



Test Planning, Test Case, Test Execution



API Test, Jmeter, Selenium Automation



Selenium Automation,Python,Java



CI/CD, Release Management

# CERTIFICATES



Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC) scrumstudy.com. Certificate ID: 855965